Uh, George, well, I brief isn't a
question.
Getting out the mud, the journey you
have to take unconventional. What did
you learn about yourself throughout that
process and why do you think that can
help you as you go to the NFL?
I feel like something I learned about
myself I'm I'm real resilient. You know,
like
I've been through a lot. I had a lot of
obstacles I had to go around to get to
where I am today. So, just like just my
resilience like just like no matter
what I was still getting my face and
just came in front of me and just like I
always find a way to like not not get
discouraged to the point to like
stopping or like changing my my my my
morals and my
my personality and who I am just like
always just to push push past it like,
you know, just no matter what it is just
you know, I always think like you know,
there's there's always going to be some
sunshine after them clouds. So, just
that's just having that mentality. So,
just keep pushing no matter no matter
the circumstances.
All right, you go ahead.
Uh, George, congratulations again. You
are the fourth SEC player to be taken by
Chris Ballard this week and you had CJ
Allen, you had AJ Halsey, and you had
Jaylen Farmer earlier today. What about
that level of play do you think will
translate or help you best when it comes
to playing in the NFL?
I I definitely say that the the speed
and physicality in SEC. It's it's a lot
of it's a lot of big guys that's moving
real fast in the SEC like just having to
fit that up on week to week. I
definitely say that's that's something
that helped me.
Joel, go ahead.
Okay.
George, who's your pass rushing
influence? Like who's
who's kind of taught you your moves and
and
what kind of style of pass rusher do you
think you are? Uh, you know,
I mean my last coach Mike Peterson he
helped me with a lot of things but like
I just me personally I just like to take
a lot of things from like a lot of a lot
of different teachers and just but Mike
Mike Peterson he definitely just like he
he he he took a deep dive for me and
just like going into like watching my
film and seeing like what what I could
do better like as far as like when it
comes when it comes to finishing like,
you know, when you do the cross chop,
you know, and just bringing that second
arm and then like with get to the
quarterback level and countering and
stuff like that. So, he he definitely
helped me with that.
Who else who else is somebody you've
pulled from?
Um,
the dog the dog trainer
um, coach coach Roe.
So, he he was at he was at Florida last
year. So, I definitely trained with him
a a whole bunch and he's very like
detailed like with with hand placement
and like, you know, catching hands and
like where I put my hands like and he
used numbers. So, I feel like that
helped me a lot.
James, go ahead. Uh, this is kind of a
selfish question. I got family from
Chicago. So, I know a lot about uh,
Simeon as they always pronounce it as
and the South Side.
Uh,
so, who's your favorite Chicago athlete
and then number two, what did the what
did the South Side of Chicago kind of
put in you as you were growing up?
Uh, I'll probably say my favorite
Chicago athlete probably going to be D
Rose.
I went to the State Farm. Like do you
have you been to Simeon so too? D Rose D
Rose different growing up bro. Like just
watching that
Well, he was different for real for
before the before the
before the surgery what? D Rose yes,
he's serious like that. But I feel like
just coming just coming from Chicago
it's it's a lot that goes on.
It's it's definitely a hard upbringing
cuz I mean the hard upbringing that
Chicago but still it definitely just
definitely helped me in my process.
And Nathan, last question.
Yeah, I've played different positions
throughout your college career
with a couple of years at edge rusher.
Obviously, you picked things up really
quickly but what what do you feel like
is the next for you or what skills do
you feel like you're going to be focused
on most as you take your career to the
next level in the NFL?
I feel like some skills I'll be working
on like in in the league it's like just
countering like just getting more fluent
with my second move, you know. I feel
like I'm I feel like I could do
a two rush
like when it comes to like getting to
the quarterback countering and just read
the stuff.
That's I feel like that's something that
I could definitely take to the next
level with.